<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bài viết on CELab</title><link>https://celab-hcmut.github.io/vi/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Bài viết on CELab</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 20:59:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://celab-hcmut.github.io/vi/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>[Seminar] Display subsystem on FPGA: from hardware to software [EN|VI]</title><link>https://celab-hcmut.github.io/vi/blog/seminar-2021-11-05/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 20:59:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://celab-hcmut.github.io/vi/blog/seminar-2021-11-05/</guid><description>Chủ đề Display subsystem on FPGA: from hardware to software
Giới thiệu Phần trình bày sẽ đề cập đến các board PYNQ-Z1, Zturn-7020, Ultra96-v1/v2.
Mục tiêu:
Giúp các kỹ sư hiểu hệ thống hiển thị hoạt động thế nào trên Linux. Các bước cơ bản để tạo thiết kế tích hợp hệ thống hiển thị (phần cứng, phần mềm, debugging). Mở rộng hệ thống với GPU, Display port over USB, Vitis-AI.</description></item><item><title>[Seminar] FPGA Hardware Acceleration Framework for Anomaly-based Intrusion Detection System in IoT [VI]</title><link>https://celab-hcmut.github.io/vi/blog/seminar-2021-10-29/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 20:59:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://celab-hcmut.github.io/vi/blog/seminar-2021-10-29/</guid><description>Chủ đề FPGA Hardware Acceleration Framework for Anomaly-based Intrusion Detection System in IoT
Abstract This study proposes a versatile framework for real-time Internet of Things (IoT) network intrusion detection using Artificial Neural Network (ANN) on heterogeneous hardware. With the increase in the volume of exchanged data, IoT networks' security has become a crucial issue. Anomaly-based intrusion detection systems (IDS) using machine learning have recently gained increased popularity, due to their generation ability to detect new attacks.</description></item></channel></rss>