<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Recents Article on CELab</title><link>https://celab-hcmut.github.io/en/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Recents Article on CELab</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 14:59:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://celab-hcmut.github.io/en/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>[Seminar Summary] Display subsystem on FPGA: from hardware to software [EN]</title><link>https://celab-hcmut.github.io/en/blog/seminar-sum-2021-11-05/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 14:59:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://celab-hcmut.github.io/en/blog/seminar-sum-2021-11-05/</guid><description>Topic Display subsystem on FPGA: from hardware to software
Introduction Goals: To help readers have the most basic understanding of the implementation of display on FPGA and display driver on Linux kernel. To help readers gain basic knowledge about Linux kernel. Brief: Display technologies on Linux: FBDEV, DRM/KMS, V4L2. Why do we choose DRM/KMS (Direct Render Manager/Kernel Mode Setting)? Because of its stability and variable of features. 5 components of DRM/KMS: Framebuffer, CRTC, Plane, Encoder, Connector.</description></item><item><title>[Seminar Summary] FPGA Hardware Acceleration Framework for Anomaly-based Intrusion Detection System in IoT [EN]</title><link>https://celab-hcmut.github.io/en/blog/seminar-sum-2021-10-29/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 01:59:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://celab-hcmut.github.io/en/blog/seminar-sum-2021-10-29/</guid><description>Topic FPGA Hardware Acceleration Framework for Anomaly-based Intrusion Detection System in IoT
Abstract This study proposes a versatile framework for real-time Internet of Things (IoT) network intrusion detection using Artificial Neural Network (ANN) on heterogeneous hardware. With the increase in the volume of exchanged data, IoT networks' security has become a crucial issue. Anomaly-based intrusion detection systems (IDS) using machine learning have recently gained increased popularity, due to their generation ability to detect new attacks.</description></item><item><title>[Seminar Summary] RISC-V SoC hardware security testing by HDL analysis [EN]</title><link>https://celab-hcmut.github.io/en/blog/seminar-sum-2021-10-15/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 12:49:27 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://celab-hcmut.github.io/en/blog/seminar-sum-2021-10-15/</guid><description>We held an online seminar recently on 15/10/2021 with the topic &amp;ldquo;RISC-V SoC hardware security testing by HDL analysis&amp;rdquo; by Le Khac Minh Dang. This is the summary of the seminar contents by the speaker.
Record video link is here. This record can be accessed by HCMUT accounts. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have any HCMUT account, please request for access permission by a Gmail, thank you. - Modifier.
Overview This topic is about doing HW security testing by hunting for bugs on a RISC-V SoC named Openpiton by analysing its RTL source code:</description></item></channel></rss>